{
  "response_code":0,
  "results":
  [
    {
     "category":"Section 2.6",
     "type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"",
     "correct_answer":"False",
     "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
     "explanation":""
     },
    {
     "category":"Section 2.6",
     "type":"multiple",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"What role does ARP play in the routing process? ",
     "correct_answer":"If a router does not know a destination device's MAC address, it sends an ARP broadcast containing the IP address and requesting the MAC address.",
     "incorrect_answers":["ARP does not play any role in the routing process. Switches use ARP to map IP addresses to MAC addresses in collision domains.","If a router does not know a destination device's IP address, it sends an ARP broadcast containing the MAC address and requesting the IP address.","If a router knows the MAC and IP address of a destination host, it sends an ARP request to update the other routers' route tables."],
     "explanation":""
     },
    {
     "category":"Section 2.6",
     "type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"",
     "correct_answer":"True",
     "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
     "explanation":""
     },
    {
     "category":"Section 2.5",
     "type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"These two of the following functions are performed by IP: Discovering the MAC address of a host and Identifying hosts with the IP address",
     "correct_answer":"False",
     "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
     "explanation":"IP is responsible for moving data through the network. It identifies hosts by the IP address and routes datagrams based on this IP address. The other functions listed here are performed by other protocols in the TCP/IP suite."
     },
    {
     "category":"Section 2.5",
     "type":"multiple",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"Which are used to identify routes through an internetwork? ",
     "correct_answer":"RIP and OSPF",
     "incorrect_answers":["BOOTP and RARP","FTP and TFPT","RARP and TCP"],
     "explanation":""
     },
    {
     "category":"Section 2.5",
     "type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "question":"ARP is used to get the MAC address of a host from its IP address.",
     "correct_answer":"True",
     "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
     "explanation":"The Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) is used to get the MAC address of a host from a known IP address. ARP is used within a subnet to get the MAC address of a device on the same subnet as the requesting device."
     },    
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"The Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP) works closely with IP in providing error and control information that helps move data packets through the internetwork."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Which is used to send email messages between mail servers? ",
      "correct_answer":"SMTP",
      "incorrect_answers":["IGMP","ARP","SNMP"],
      "explanation":"The Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP) is used to route electronic mail between mail servers. The Post Office Protocol (POP3) is used by email clients to retrieve email from mail servers."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"DHCP is used to assign IP addresses to hosts.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":"The Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) is used for delivering IP addresses to network hosts."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"An Internet server has a single network interface that has been assigned an IP address. The server is running both the FTP and HTTP services. A client computer initiates a session with the HTTP server. The HTTP request from the client routed to the correct service running on the server using Routing Information Protocol (RIP).",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"An Internet server has a single network interface that has been assigned an IP address. The server is running both the FTP and HTTP services. A client computer initiates a session with the HTTP server. How is the HTTP request from the client routed to the correct service running on the server? ",
      "correct_answer":"Port or socket number",
      "incorrect_answers":["IP address","Session ID","Sequence number"],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"These two of the following functions are performed by IP: Identifying hosts with the IP address and Routing datagrams to hosts",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":"IP is responsible for moving data through the network. It identifies hosts by the IP address and routes datagrams based on this IP address. The other functions listed here are performed by other protocols in the TCP/IP suite."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A client computer starts to download some files from an FTP server named FTPsvr1. While the first download is in progress, the user opens a second instance of the FTP program and initiates a second download. The server and the client use CRC to keep each download separate.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"Communication instances are kept separate by session IDs. Each communication instance is identified with a session ID. Port or socket numbers are used to identify a service running on the server. For example, FTP uses ports 20 and 21 to send communications to the FTP service running on the server. Both sessions would use the same port number(s) to communicate. Sequence numbers are used in packets to make sure that packets can be reassembled in the proper order and to identify lost packets. The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is used in a packet or a frame to identify errors within the packet or the frame. The IP address identifies a network interface."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A client computer starts to download some files from an FTP server named FTPsvr1. While the first download is in progress, the user opens a second instance of the FTP program and initiates a second download. What does the server and the client use to keep each download separate?",
      "correct_answer":"Session ID",
      "incorrect_answers":["Port or socket numbers","Sequence numbers","IP Address"],
      "explanation":"Communication instances are kept separate by session IDs. Each communication instance is identified with a session ID. Port or socket numbers are used to identify a service running on the server. For example, FTP uses ports 20 and 21 to send communications to the FTP service running on the server. Both sessions would use the same port number(s) to communicate. Sequence numbers are used in packets to make sure that packets can be reassembled in the proper order and to identify lost packets. The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is used in a packet or a frame to identify errors within the packet or the frame. The IP address identifies a network interface."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A client computer starts to download some files from an FTP server named FTPsvr1. While the first download is in progress, the user opens a second instance of the FTP program and initiates a second download. The server and the client use sequence numbers to keep each download separate.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"Communication instances are kept separate by session IDs. Each communication instance is identified with a session ID. Port or socket numbers are used to identify a service running on the server. For example, FTP uses ports 20 and 21 to send communications to the FTP service running on the server. Both sessions would use the same port number(s) to communicate. Sequence numbers are used in packets to make sure that packets can be reassembled in the proper order and to identify lost packets. The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is used in a packet or a frame to identify errors within the packet or the frame. The IP address identifies a network interface."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The purpose of the CRC in network communications is to re-assemble packets into their original order.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is a mathematical calculation added to each frame. Its purpose is to detect when a frame arrives that has been corrupted. The sending device calculates the CRC and adds it to the frame. The receiving device calculates the CRC when the frame is received. If the CRCs do not match, the frame has been corrupted or altered. The most common method of correcting errors is to request retransmission of the original frame. Lost packets are detected by missing sequence numbers or missing acknowledgements. Packet sequence numbers are also used to re-assemble packets into their original order. Flow control uses special messages to speed up or slow down the rate of data transmission."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"What is the purpose of the CRC in network communications? ",
      "correct_answer":"Detect data errors",
      "incorrect_answers":["Request retransmission of lost packets","Detect lost packets","Correct data errors"],
      "explanation":"The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is a mathematical calculation added to each frame. Its purpose is to detect when a frame arrives that has been corrupted. The sending device calculates the CRC and adds it to the frame. The receiving device calculates the CRC when the frame is received. If the CRCs do not match, the frame has been corrupted or altered. The most common method of correcting errors is to request retransmission of the original frame. Lost packets are detected by missing sequence numbers or missing acknowledgements. Packet sequence numbers are also used to re-assemble packets into their original order. Flow control uses special messages to speed up or slow down the rate of data transmission."
      },
    {
      "category":"Section 2.5",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The purpose of the CRC in network communications is to request retransmission of lost packets",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"The Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) is a mathematical calculation added to each frame. Its purpose is to detect when a frame arrives that has been corrupted. The sending device calculates the CRC and adds it to the frame. The receiving device calculates the CRC when the frame is received. If the CRCs do not match, the frame has been corrupted or altered. The most common method of correcting errors is to request retransmission of the original frame. Lost packets are detected by missing sequence numbers or missing acknowledgements. Packet sequence numbers are also used to re-assemble packets into their original order. Flow control uses special messages to speed up or slow down the rate of data transmission."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Physical=Logical device identification, path identification and selection.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Which of the following are functions of the MAC sublayer in the OSI model? ",
      "correct_answer":"Defining a unique hardware address for each device on the network and letting devices on the network have access to the LAN.",
      "incorrect_answers":["Letting devices on the network have access to the LAN and mapping hardware addresses to link-layer addresses.","Mapping hardware addresses to link-layer addresses and defining a unique hardware address for each device on the network.","Defining a unique hardware address for each device on the network and creating routing tables based on MAC addresses."],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Network=Logical device identification, path identification and selection.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Transport=Convert data to 0s and 1s, bit signaling and synchronization.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
      }, 
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Physical=Convert data to 0s and 1s, bit signaling and synchronization.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      }, 
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Transport=Flow control, reliable data transfer, windowing, segmentation, and sequencing.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      }, 
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions:  Network=Logical topology, hardware addresses, media access, framing.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
      {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following items describe the    functions performed at various OSI model layers: 1-Logical topology, hardware addresses, media access, framing. 2-Logical device identification, path identification and selection. 3-Flow control, reliable data transfer, windowing, segmentation, and sequencing. 4-Convert data to 0s and 1s, bit signaling and synchronization.   Which of the following correctly identifies the layers that perform each of the functions listed here? ",
      "correct_answer":"Data Link, Network, Transport, Physical",
      "incorrect_answers":["Network, Data Link, Transport, Physical","Transport, Network, Physical, Data Link","Physical, Transport, Network, Data Link"],
      "explanation":"The following OSI model layers correspond to the following functions: Data Link-Logical topology, hardware addresses, media access, framing.    Network-Logical device identification, path identification and selection. Transport-Flow control, reliable data transfer, windowing, segmentation, and sequencing.  Physical-Convert data to 0s and 1s, bit signaling and synchronization."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The following OSI model layer corresponds to the following functions: Transport=Flow control, reliable data transfer, windowing, segmentation, and sequencing.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking ",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"169.254.0.1 - 169.254.255.254 is one of the ranges of private IP addresses that are commonly used behind a NAT router.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"169.254.0.1 - 169.254.255.254 is the range of IP addresses assigned to Windows DHCP clients if a DHCP server does not assign the client an IP address. This range is known as the Automatic Private IP Addressing (APIPA) range. The other three ranges listed in this question are defined as the private IP addresses from RFC 1918 which are commonly used behind a NAT server."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Given that an IPv4 address is a 32-bit binary number represented in four octets (four 8-bit values), which of the following are valid IP addresses? ",
      "correct_answer":"137.65.1.1",
      "incorrect_answers":["137.65.1.257","256.1.1.1","10.256.1.1"],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The correct binary form of the decimal IP address 192.168.1.1 is 11000000.10101000.00000001.00000001",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A workstation has been assigned the following IP addressing information: IP address: 192.168.1.26, Subnet mask: 255.255.255.0, Default gateway: 192.168.1.254, DNS server: 192.168.1. Given this information, what is the IP address of the network where this host resides? ",
      "correct_answer":"192.168.1.0",
      "incorrect_answers":["192.168.0.0","192.0.0.0","192.168.1.255"],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"127.99.1.155 and 10.244.12.16 are private IP addresses.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"Private addresses fall within the following range: 10.0.0.0 to 10.255.255.255, 172.16.0.0 to 172.31.255.255 and 192.168.0.0 to 192.168.255.255. Private addresses are used only within a private network, and cannot be used on the Internet. A service such as Network Address Translation (NAT) is required to translate private addresses into a public address."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"What is the correct decimal form of this binary IP address: 00001010.00000000.01100100.00011101 ",
      "correct_answer":"10.0.100.29",
      "incorrect_answers":["137.0.65.11","192.0.1.26","10.0.65.29"],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" 142.15.6.1  is a valid IP address for a host on a public network.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation": "A public network is a network that does not limit traffic to members of a corporation or other group. The Internet is an example of a public network. Certain sets of IP addresses are reserved for private networks only and cannot be used on public networks. They are: 10.0.0.0 - 10.255.255.255, 172.16.0.0 - 172.31.255.255 and 192.168.0.0 - 192.168.255.255"
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A network host has an IP address of 137.65.1.2 assigned to it. Given that the network uses the default classful subnet mask, what is the default routing prefix for this address? ",
      "correct_answer":"/16",
      "incorrect_answers":["/24","/8","/32"],
      "explanation":"Because 137.65.1.2 falls within the range of 128.0.0.0 to 191.255.255.255, it is a class B address and uses a default subnet mask of 255.255.0.0. Therefore, the default routing prefix is /16. /8 is the default routing prefix for class A IP addresses, while /24 is the default routing prefix for class C IP addresses. A default routing prefix of /32 would use all available bits in an IPv4 address for the network address, leaving no host addresses available."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A workstation on your company network that has Internet access is most likely to be assigned a public IP address.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":"To connect a private network, home or business, to the Internet, you must have a router with a public IP address. The public address allows hosts on the Internet to send packets to the router. To connect a private network, home or business, to the Internet, you must have a router with a public IP address. The public address allows hosts on the Internet to send packets to the router. When connecting a private network to the Internet, only the router interface connected to the Internet needs a public address. You can then use Network Address Translation (NAT) and assign private addresses to hosts on your private network (including all routers on the private network). The NAT router translates your private addresses into the public address. You can even use NAT to place publicly available hosts, such as web servers, on the private network (although these servers are often placed in a special subnet connected to the Internet and assigned public addresses). With port address translation, incoming messages sent to the publicly available servers are relayed to the private network. Servers that hold confidential data, such as database servers, are normally placed on the private network, and can only be contacted directly by the necessary devices (such as a web server)."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" A network host has an IP address of 10.10.0.2 assigned to it. Given that the network uses the default classful subnet mask, what is the default routing prefix for this address?",
      "correct_answer":"/8",
      "incorrect_answers":["/24","/16","/32"],
      "explanation":"Because 10.10.0.2 falls within the range of 1.0.0.0 to 126.255.255.255, it is a class A address and uses a default subnet mask of 255.0.0.0. Therefore, the default routing prefix is /8. /16 is the default routing prefix for class B IP addresses, while /24 is the default routing prefix for class C IP addresses. A default routing prefix of /32 would use all available bits in an IPv4 address for the network address, leaving no host addresses available."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Your network uses a network address of 137.65.0.0 with a subnet mask of 255.255.0.0.  65534 addresses are available for assignment to network hosts on this network. ",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":"Given a network address and subnet mask, you can have 2 to the nth power - 2 hosts per subnet. Begin by converting the subnet mask to a binary number. To find the number of valid hosts, n = the number of unmasked bits in the mask. In this example, there are 16 unmasked bits in the mask. Therefore, the number of available hosts is 2 to the 16th power - 2, which equals 65534."
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You want to implement an Ethernet network using the 1000BaseT standard using the minimum hardware specifications possible. Which of the following should you include in your plan",
      "correct_answer":"Cat5e twisted pair cable and RJ-45 connectors",
      "incorrect_answers":["Multi-mode fiber optic cable and LC connectors","Cat5 twisted pair cable","Single-mode fiber optic cable and ST connectors","Cat4 twisted pair cable"],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Which of the following accurately describe how switches and hubs work?",
      "correct_answer":["Switches use the hardware address in the frame to send it only to the port where the device is located, A hub repeats frames to all ports, regardless of the destination address."],
      "incorrect_answers":["A switch uses the logical addresses in a packet to send it through the correct port to all VLANs defined on that port.","A hub uses the hardware address in the frame to forward it to the hosts on the VLAN that corresponds to that address.", "Switches and hubs repeat frames to all ports, regardless of the destination address."],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You need to connect several network devices together using twisted pair Ethernet cables. Assuming Auto-MDI/MDIX is not enabled on these devices, you would connect Router to switch using Straight-through Ethernet cable",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You need to connect several network devices together using twisted pair Ethernet cables. Assuming Auto-MDI/MDIX is not enabled on these devices, you would connect Workstation to switch using Straight-through Ethernet cable",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You need to connect several network devices together using twisted pair Ethernet cables. Assuming Auto-MDI/MDIX is not enabled on these devices, you would connect Switch to switch using Crossover Ethernet cable ",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You need to connect several network devices together using twisted pair Ethernet cables. Assuming Auto-MDI/MDIX is not enabled on these devices, you would connect Workstation to router using Crossover Ethernet cable",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":["False","",""],
      "explanation":""
      },
    {
      "category":"Networking",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":" You need to connect several network devices together using twisted pair Ethernet cables. Assuming Auto-MDI/MDIX is not enabled on these devices, you would connect Router to router using Straight-through Ethernet cable",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":["True","",""],
      "explanation":""
    }
  ]
}
